Guide to the William Graham Sumner Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1854-(1863-1909)-1948; Series I; 14' (36 boxes)
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - Peres, Israel H. (*), 1896-1903 (Box 18, Folder 498)
    - Perkins, Arthur - Raymond Perrin, 1882, 1884-1886, 1891, undated (Box 18, Folder 499)
    - Perry A. L., 1873-1883 (Box 18, Folder 500)
    - Perry, C. B. - Franklin B. Pfeiffer, 1864, 1872-1875, 1877-1878, 1880, 1882-1884, 1886-1887, 1898, 1900-1901, 1903-1904, 1908, undated (Box 18, Folder 501)
      - Pell, Mary - Henry Pepper, 1878, 1880, 1882-1884, 1887, 1889, 1906-1907, undated (Box 18, Folder 497)
    - Phelps, E. J. - William Walter Phelps, 1872, 1875-1877, 1882-1884, 1889, 1896, 1898, undated (Box 18, Folder 502)
    - Phenix, George P., 1897, 1900, 1903-1904 (Box 18, Folder 503)
    - Phenix, Maria E. - Joseph P. Philips, 1881, 1884-1886, 1896-1897, 1899, 1904, 1908, undated (Box 18, Folder 504)
    - Phillips, Andrew W. (*), 1873-1876, 1881-1893, 1896-1908, undated (Box 19, Folder 505-508)
    - H. G. Phillips and Company - William Phillips, 1876, 1877, 1907-1908, undated (Box 19, Folder 509)
    - Philpott, Henry J. (*), 1881-1882 (Box 19, Folder 510-511)
    - Philpott, Henry J., 1883-1884 (Box 19, Folder 512)
    - Philpott, Henry J. (*), 1887, undated (Box 19, Folder 513)
      See also: box 17, folder 445
      See also: Iowa State Leader, box 13, folder 352
    - Phisterer, Fred - John N. Pierce, 1878, 1881-1882, 1884, 1888-1890, 1907, undated (Box 19, Folder 514)
    - Pierce, Paul - F. H. Platt, 1874, 1876, 1880, 1882-1885, 1887, 1895, 1899-1900, 1904 (Box 19, Folder 515)
    - Platt, O. H. - Popular Science Monthly, 1874, 1881-1886, 1889, 1891, 1907, undated (Box 19, Folder 516)
    - Porter, Edward C. (*), 1869-1870 (Box 19, Folder 517)
    - Porter, Edwin L. (*), 1886-1887, 1900 (Box 19, Folder 518)
    - Porter, John Addison (*), 1885, 1887-1888, undated (Box 19, Folder 519)
    - Porter, Noah (*), 1863-1888 (Box 19, Folder 520)
    - Porter, Luther N. - Frederick Potter, 1870, 1875, 1881, 1883, 1891, 1895 (Box 19, Folder 521)
    - Potter, Henry C. (*), 1869-1871 (Box 19, Folder 522)
    - Potter, Howard - E. Parmalee Prentice, 1877-1878, 1880-1881, 1884, 1887, 1890, 1903-1904, undated (Box 19, Folder 523)
    - Prentice, Samuel O. (*), 1878-1882 (Box 19, Folder 524)
    - Price, Lee and Atkins Company - W. Price, 1880-1881, 1901, 1908, undated (Box 19, Folder 525)
    - Price, William (*), 1893, 1896 (Box 19, Folder 526)
    - Price, William (*), 1897-1898, 1906, 1908 (Box 19, Folder 527)
      See also: box 6, folder 156
    - Prieto, Guillermo - Puritan Publishing Company, 1879, 1881-1889, 1893, 1896-1898, undated (Box 19, Folder 528)
    - G. P. Putman and Sons (*), 1872-1906 (Box 19, Folder 529-531)
    - Putman, Herbert - C. J. Quintart, 1870, 1882-1886, 1898, 1901, undated (Box 19, Folder 532)
    - Raffalovich, Arthur, undated (Box 20, Folder 533)
    - Raffalovich, Sophie, 1883-1885 (Box 20, Folder 534)
    - Raffalovich, Sophie (*), 1886-1887 (Box 20, Folder 535)
    - Raffalovich, Sophie (*), 1888-1889, undated (Box 20, Folder 536)
    - Ragle, Samuel B. - Anson D. Randolph, 1869-1870, 1876, 1879, 1885, 1888, undated (Box 20, Folder 537)
    - Randolph, J. F., Jr., 1864-1865 (Box 20, Folder 538)
    - Rappley, W. G. - L. Redman, 1878, 1883, 1886, 1891, 1895, 1901, 1903 (Box 20, Folder 539)
    - Reform Club (*), 1888-1908 (Box 20, Folder 540)
    - Reed, A. J. - E. G. Reid, 1875-1876, 1878, 1880-1883, 1885-1886, 1890, 1898, 1908 (Box 20, Folder 541)
    - Reid, Kersey C. - James B. Reynolds, 1871, 1873-1874, 1876-1877, 1883-1885, 1887, 1890, 1896, 1900-1902, undated (Box 20, Folder 542)
    - Rhoades, John H. (*), 1899 (Box 20, Folder 543)
    - Rhoads, Dudley - James Rice, 1877-1879, 1882-1884, 1887, undated (Box 20, Folder 544)
    - Rich, Edgar J. - William Richards, 1869, 1875, 1883, 1886, 1890, 1892, 1896, undated (Box 20, Folder 545)
    - Richardson, C. F. - R. M. Richmond, 1874, 1877-1883, 1886, 1889, 1900 (Box 20, Folder 546)
    - Sidney S. Rider and Brother - D. C. Robbins, 1869-1871, 1875, 1878, 1880, 1882, 1885, 1890-1891, 1895-1896, 1903, 1907, undated (Box 20, Folder 547)
    - Robbins, Edward B., 1877-1887, 1895-1899 (Box 20, Folder 548)
      See also: box 18, folder 475
    - Roberts, Charles A. - Peter Roberts, 1873, 1883, 1895, 1901, 1903-1904 (Box 20, Folder 549)
    - Robertson, Henry - William C. Robinson, 1874-1875, 1879, 1883-1884, 1886, 1889, 1896, 1903, 1908-1909 (Box 20, Folder 550)
    - Robson, James A. - Rochester Political Economy Club, 1876, 1881-1882, 1890, 1897-1899, 1903, 1906 (Box 20, Folder 551)
    - Rockwell, Alfred P. (*), 1872-1881, 1883, 1885-1887, 1897, 1899, 1900, undated (Box 20, Folder 552-554)
    - Rockwell, Diana (*), 1897-1898, 1900-1901, 1904 January - Sep, 1906, 1908-1909, undated (Box 20, Folder 555-557)
    - Rockwell, K. V. - L. Harding Rogers, Jr., 1872, 1874, 1877-1879, 1889, 1903, 1908, undated (Box 20, Folder 558)
    - Romeike, Henry - T. C. Root, 1870, 1874, 1877, 1881, 1884-1890, undated (Box 20, Folder 559)
    - Romero, M.
      See: Guillermo Prieto, box 19, folder 528
    - Roper, Charles F. (*), 1869-1870 (Box 20, Folder 560)
    - Herman Rosenthal and Company - William E. Rowland, 1877, 1882-1884, 1886-1887, 1900-1901, 1904, 1906, undated (Box 20, Folder 561)
    - Royall, William - George Ryer and Company, 1867, 1869-1870, 1876, 1880, 1882-1885, 1890-1892, 1895, 1897, 1908, undated (Box 20, Folder 562)
    - Rylance, J. H. (*), (1869)-1871 (Box 20, Folder 563)
    - Sackett, Charles E. - George C. St. John, 1878, 1883-1884, 1895, 1901, 1908 (Box 21, Folder 564)
    - St. John, H. W. (*), 1880-1908 (Box 21, Folder 565)
    - St. John, Samuel B. - Frank K. Sanders, 1872-1874, 1887-1888, 1893, 1897-1898, 1900-1901, undated (Box 21, Folder 566)
    - Sanderson, George A. - Saturday Morning Club of Hartford, 1876, 1878, 1881-1883, 1885, 1888, 1890, 1908, undated (Box 21, Folder 567)
    - P. H. B. Saunders and Sons (*), 1875-1883, 1908 (Box 21, Folder 568)
    - Saunders, R. C. - Decatur M. Sawyer, 1878, 1885-1887 (Box 21, Folder 569)
    - Sawyer, George P. (*), 1875-1889 (Box 21, Folder 570)
    - Sawyer, Henry E. - J. G. Schaeffer, 1869, 1882, 1884, 1886, 1900 (Box 21, Folder 571)
    - Schaff, Philip (*), 1870-1872, 1876 (Box 21, Folder 572)
    - Schaus, William - G. Schwab, 1871, 1873-1876, 1878, 1881-1882, 1887-1891, 1899, 1905-1906 (Box 21, Folder 573)
    - Schwab, John C. (*), 1886-1908, undated (Box 21, Folder 574-575)
    - Science - Carl W. Scover, 1869-1871, 1873, 1883, 1887, 1891, undated (Box 21, Folder 576)
    - Scribner, Armstrong and Company - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1870, 1872-1874, 1878, 1882, 1884, 1890, 1895, 1901, 1903, 1906 (Box 21, Folder 577)
    - Scribner's Monthly, 1877-1881 (Box 21, Folder 578)
    - Scudder, Harvey - D. W. Seamed, 1874, 1889, 1898, 1903 (Box 21, Folder 579)
    - Sears, J. M., 1879, 1883-1884, 1897-1904 (Box 21, Folder 580)
    - Sears, Sarah C. - Frederick Seymour, 1871-1876, 1881, 1883-1884, 1886, 1895, 1897, 1900, 1908, undated (Box 21, Folder 581)
    - Seymour, John S. - S. D. Seymour, 1879, 1882, 1885, 1890-1891, 1901, undated (Box 21, Folder 582)
    - Seymour, Storrs O. (*), 1882-1883 (Box 21, Folder 583)
    - Seymour, Thomas D. (*), 1885-1895 (Box 21, Folder 584)
    - Shaffrath, Paul - Henry E. Sharpe, 1881, 1884, 1889-1890, 1904, undated (Box 21, Folder 585)
    - Sharpe, Louisa D. (*), 1887-1892, 1895, 1897, 1900, 1903, 1907 (Box 21, Folder 586)
    - Sharpe, Lucian - John T. Shaw, 1870-1872, 1880, 1882-1883, 1887-1889 (Box 21, Folder 587)
    - Shearman, Thomas G. (*), 1880-1883, undated (Box 21, Folder 588)
      See also: Henry Philipott, box 19, folders 510-513
    - Sheffield, George (*), 1863-1865, 1868, 1872-1873, 1877, 1899, undated (Box 21, Folder 589)
    - Sheean, J. B. - C. S. Sheldon, 1878, 1880, 1887, 1908 (Box 21, Folder 590)
    - Sheldon, Charles A., 1893-1904 (Box 21, Folder 591)
    - Sheldon, E. P. - Henry W. Shelton, 1869, 1882-1883, 1885, 1887-1888, 1891, 1901 (Box 21, Folder 592)
    - Shepard, Charles E. - W. W. Sherman, 1864, 1866, 1873, 1875, 1878, 1880, 1885, 1890, 1899, 1907, undated (Box 21, Folder 593)
    - C. L. Sherrill and Co. - Augustine Simmons, 1872, 1875-1879, 1885, 1887, 1891, 1893, 1897, 1902, 1907-1908, undated (Box 21, Folder 594)
    - Simmons, H. M. - G. H. Skinner, 1875, 1876, 1883, 1886, 1888, 1889, 1896, 1898, 1908, undated (Box 21, Folder 595)
    - Skull and Bones, undated (Box 22, Folder 596)
    - Slicer, Thomas R. - John P. Slocum, 1869, 1873, 1875, 1883, 1885, 1893, 1898 (Box 22, Folder 597)
    - Small, Albion W. - Charles R. Smith, 1872, 1874, 1878, 1881, 1885-1887, 1890, 1895, 1899, 1903, undated (Box 22, Folder 598)
    - Smith, Edwin A. - Franklin Smith, 1880, 1882, 1886-1888, 1901, 1903, undated (Box 22, Folder 599)
    - Smith, G. G. - R. G. Smith, 1876, 1883, 1885, 1887, 1888, 1893, 1897, 1899, 1900, 1906, undated (Box 22, Folder 600)
    - Smith, Raymond - Smithsonian Institute, 1878-1881, 1884-1885, 1887, 1895, 1906-1907 (Box 22, Folder 601)
    - Smiting, W. A. - Society for Savings, 1870, 1879, 1882, 1884, 1885, 1889, 1895, 1897, 1898, 1901, 1904, 1908 (Box 22, Folder 602)
    - Sollau, O. H. - Southern New England Telephone, 1873, 1874, 1882, 1890, 1898, 1899, 1901, 1903, 1908 (Box 22, Folder 603)
    - Southworth, George C. V. (*), 1863-1865, 1869, 1885, 1890, 1903, 1908 (Box 22, Folder 604)
    - Spaulding, Randall - E. Spencer, 1869, 1885, 1886, undated (Box 22, Folder 605)
    - Spencer, Herbert, 1883-1884 (Box 22, Folder 606)
    - Spencer, S. - Watson Sperry, 1875-1878, 1880, 1882, 1883, 1885, 1896 (Box 22, Folder 607)
    - Sperry, Watson
      See: box 8, folder 213
    - Spofford, A. R. - Paul Streuzpointner, 1874, 1876, 1879, 1884, 1896, 1898 (Box 22, Folder 608)
    - Stallo, John B. - E. D. Stark, 1882-1884, 1886-1888, 1897 (Box 22, Folder 609)
    - Stark, William M. - Frederick Starr, 1874, 1883, 1884, 1888, 1889, 1890, 1893 (Box 22, Folder 610)
    - Starr, Judson - George L. Stebbins, 1869, 1871, 1882-1887, 1895, 1897, 1898, 1908 (Box 22, Folder 611)
    - Stechert, Gustav E. - W.K. Stetson, 1877, 1879, 1881, 1882, 1884, 1885, 1889, 1897, 1899, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 612)
    - Stevens, Albert C. - Philip B. Stewart, 1873, 1876, 1877, 1882-1884, 1890, 1893, 1899, 1900-1901, 1903, undated (Box 22, Folder 613)
    - Stillman, James A. - Louis A. Stimson, 1866-1868, 1884, 1888, 1898, 1899, 1903, undated (Box 22, Folder 614)
    - Stoddard, Cootie - Anson Phelps Stokes, 1877, 1879, 1888, 1890, 1891, 1903-1904, undated (Box 22, Folder 615)
    - Stokes, Anson Phelps, Jr. (*), 1895, 1900-1901, 1903-1904, 1907-1909 (Box 22, Folder 616)
    - Stokes, Frederick A. - A. E. Stone, 1874, 1903 (Box 22, Folder 617)
    - Stone, F. D. (*), 1890-1892, 1895 (Box 22, Folder 618)
    - Stone, J. B. - F. Strong, 1871, 1877, 1882, 1884-1885, 1889-1890, 1902, undated (Box 22, Folder 619)
    - Strong, George A. - Sumerwell, Shoup, and Vermilya, 1871, 1874-1877, 1880, 1884, 1897, 1899-1900, undated (Box 22, Folder 620)
    - Sumner, Alfred, 1899 (Box 22, Folder 621)
    - Sumner, Alice (*), 1872-1874, 1876, 1880, 1883, 1886 July - September 1888 Aug, undated (Box 22, Folder 622-627)
    - Sumner, C. F. - E. M. Sumner, 1886 (Box 22, Folder 628)
    - Sumner, Eliot, 1890, 1895 (Box 23, Folder 629)
    - Sumner, Eliot (*), 1897 February - June (Box 23, Folder 630)
    - Sumner, Eliot, 1897 July - May, 1898 August - Oct, 1899-1901 Mar, 1901 May - December (Box 23, Folder 631-643)
    - Sumner, Eliot (*), 1903-1904, 1906-1909, undated (Box 23, Folder 644-646)
    - Sumner, Mrs. Eliot, undated (Box 23, Folder 647)
      See also: box 20, folders 555-557
    - Sumner, Esther, 1863 Jun, November - Dec, 1864-1869, 1881, 1885, undated (Box 23, Folder 648-651)
    - Sumner, G. W. - George Sumner, 1884, 1886, 1889 (Box 23, Folder 652)
    - Sumner, Graham (*), 1900 May - Nov, 1887, 1890, 1895, 1897-1899, 1900?, 1901-1903 (Box 23, Folder 653-656)
    - Sumner, Graham (*), 1903 October - Dec, 1903 Post, 1904, 1906 February - Jul, 1906 November -1908 Jul, undated (Box 24, Folder 657-666)
    - Sumner, Mrs. Graham, undated (Box 24, Folder 667)
      See also: box 31, folder 868-869
    - Sumner, Henry (*), 1881 January - 1884 July (Box 24, Folder 668-671)
    - Sumner, Henry, 1903-1904, 1906, 1908, undated (Box 24, Folder 672-673)
    - Sumner, Jeannie, 1870 April 25 - 1870 May 24 (Box 25, Folder 674)
    - Sumner, Jeannie (*), 1870 May 26 - 1870 June 18 (Box 25, Folder 675)
    - Sumner, Jeannie, 1870 June 21 - 1870 July 12, 1870 July 14 - 1870 August 7, 1870 August 9 - 1870 August 24, 1870 September 18 - 1870 September 29, 1870 October 1 - 1870 October 10, 1870 October 12 - 1870 November 6 (Box 25, Folder 676-681)
    - Sumner, Jeannie (TL), 1870 May 5 - 1870 September 24 (Box 25, Folder 682)
    - Sumner, Jeannie (*), 1873-1878, 1881 Jun, 1882 January - 1886 Apr, 1886 July g, 1886-1890 Apr, August (Box 26, Folder 683-692)
    - Sumner, Jeannie, 1890 December (Box 26, Folder 693)
    - Sumner, Jeannie (*), 1890, 1891 March; 1893 September - Nov; 1895, (1897 March - Apr?), (1897 May - Jun?), (1897?) (Box 26, Folder 694-698)
    - Sumner, Jeannie, 1899 May 1900 January - April (Box 26, Folder 699)
    - Sumner, Jeannie (*), 1900 May - June (Box 26, Folder 700)
    - Sumner, Jeannie, 1903 July (Box 26, Folder 701)
    - Sumner, Jeannie (*), undated (Box 26, Folder 702-703)
    - Sumner, Jeannie (NYC) (*), undated (Box 26, Folder 704)
    - Sumner, Jeannie (Morristown and Cambridge) (*), undated (Box 26, Folder 705)
    - Sumner, Jeannie (*), undated (Box 26, Folder 706-711)
    - Sumner, Jeannie (Westhampton) (*), undated (Box 26, Folder 712-714)
    - Sumner, Jeannie (E. Gloucester, Mass.) (*), undated (Box 26, Folder 715)
    - Sumner, Jeannie (Atlantic City), undated (Box 26, Folder 716)
    - Sumner, Jeannie (Atlantic City) (*), undated (Box 26, Folder 717)
    - Sumner, Jeannie, undated (Box 26, Folder 718)
    - Sumner, John O., 1887 (Box 26, Folder 719)
    - Sumner, Joseph, 1863 September 9 - 1863 November 1, 1864 January 31 - 1864 December, 1865 May 24 - 1865 August 20, 1866 October - 29 1866 December 5 (Box 27, Folder 720-725)
    - Sumner, Joseph (*), 1867-1868, 1870 January - September (Box 27, Folder 726-727)
    - Sumner, Joseph, 1871-1873 (Box 27, Folder 728)
    - Sumner, Joseph (*), 1874-1875 (Box 27, Folder 729)
    - Sumner, Joseph, 1876 September - Nov, 1877-1878 (Box 27, Folder 730-731)
    - Sumner, Joseph (*), 1879, 1881, 1884-1890 (Box 27, Folder 732-735)
    - Sumner, Joseph, 1891-1895, undated (Box 27, Folder 736)
    - Sumner, Joseph, 1899-1900, 1901, 1906 January - May (Box 27, Folder 737-738)
    - Sumner, Joseph R. (*), 1906 June - Dec, 1907-1908, undated (Box 27, Folder 739-741)
    - Sumner, Kate E., 1864, 1865 Apr, Sep, 1866 Feb, June 1869 Feb, Dec, 1883-1885, undated (Box 27, Folder 742-746)
    - Sumner, "Lizzie", undated (Box 27, Folder 747)
    - Sumner, Thomas, 1863 July 26, 1863 October - Nov, 1864 February 1864 May, 1864 June 26, 1864 Aug, October, December, 1865 January, April, June, July, 1865 September 24, 1865 December 8, 1866 January - February, 1866 April - Nov, 1867 July - Nov, 1868 January - Nov, 1869 (Box 27, Folder 748-760)
    - Sumner, Thomas, 1870 March - Oct, 1871 January - Nov, 1872 January - December (Box 28, Folder 761-763)
    - Sumner, Thomas, 1873 January - December (Box 28, Folder 763a)
    - Sumner, Thomas, 1874 January - November (Box 28, Folder 764)
    - Sumner, Thomas (*), 1875 February - 1876 December (Box 28, Folder 765)
    - Sumner, Thomas (*), 1877 January - November (Box 28, Folder 765a)
    - Sumner, Thomas (*), 1878 January - November (Box 28, Folder 766)
    - Sumner, Thomas, 1879 January - Jul, 1880 June (Box 28, Folder 766a)
    - Sumner, Thomas (*), undated (Box 28, Folder 767)
    - Sumner, William D. - Noah H. Swayne II, 1873-1874, 1877, 1886, 1888, 1898 (Box 28, Folder 768)
    - Sweet, Belle - Louis J. Swinburne, 1880, 1883, 1889-1890, 1906, 1908, undated (Box 28, Folder 769)
    - Syle, Louis DuPont (*), 1879-1890 (Box 28, Folder 770-771)
    - Sylvester, J. W., 1878-1892 (Box 28, Folder 772)
    - Syphai, Fred B. - William H. Taft, 1877-1880, 1882, 1887, 1899, 1904, 1906, undated (Box 28, Folder 773)
    - Tajiri, Quajiro - Alfred Taylor, 1876, 1878-1879, 1883-1886, 1889, 1901, 1904, undated (Box 28, Folder 774)
    - Taylor, C. H. - Henry J. Ten Eyck, 1870, 1872-1873, 1876, 1882-1887, 1889, 1908, undated (Box 28, Folder 775)
    - Terry, E. R. - Lewis G. Tewksbury, 1877-1878, 1886, 1896, 1898, undated (Box 28, Folder 776)
    - Thacher, Alfred B. - Sherman D. Thacher, 1886, 1889, undated (Box 28, Folder 777)
    - Thacher, Thomas A., 1878-1879, 1881, 1884, undated (Box 28, Folder 778)
    - Thacher, Thomas - C. M. Thomas, 1869, 1880, 1882-1885, 1888, 1896, 1898, 1900-1901 (Box 28, Folder 779)
    - Thomas, Edwin S. - C. H. Thompson, 1871-1872, 1875, 1877-1878, 1883, 1885, 1895-1896, 1898, 1901, 1904, 1908, undated (Box 28, Folder 780)
    - Thompson, C. Mildred - Tiffany and Company, 1868, 1871, 1878, 1883, 1885-1886, 1893, 1901, 1903-1904, 1906-1908 (Box 28, Folder 781)
    - Tiffany, C. C., undated (Box 28, Folder 782)
    - Tighe, Ambrose - George P. Torrence, 1874, 1876, 1881-1886, 1895, 1897-1899, undated (Box 28, Folder 783)
    - Torrey, Bright, and Capon - A. W. Treadwell, 1874-1875, 1879, 1882, 1884-1887, 1891, 1896-1897, 1900, 1904, undated (Box 28, Folder 784)
    - Tremaine, C. H. B. - Mason Trowbridge, 1876-1878, 1882, 1884, 1886, 1904 (Box 28, Folder 785)
    - Trowbridge, Thomas R., 1874-1876, undated (Box 28, Folder 786)
    - Trumbull, J. H. - George Tufts, 1876, 1880, 1882-1885 (Box 28, Folder 787)
    - Tulsifer, J. D. - John P. Tuttle, 1870-1873, 1880, 1882-1884, 1886-1887, 1897 (Box 28, Folder 788)
    - Tuttle, W. R. (*), 1895-1900, undated (Box 28, Folder 789)
    - Twing, A. J. - Morris F. Tyler, 1872, 1874, 1880-1881, 1884, 1887, 1895, 1903-1904, undated (Box 28, Folder 790)
    - Udell, William D. - United States Department of Commerce and Labor, 1872, 1880, 1884, 1886, 1889, 1891, 1895, 1898-1900, 1903, 1906, undated (Box 28, Folder 791)
    - United States Department of the Interior (*), 1872-1874, 1883, 1886-1887, 1895, 1899 (Box 29, Folder 792)
    - United States Department of State - United States Post Office, 1875-1876, 1878, 1883, 1885-1887, 1890, 1897-1898, undated (Box 29, Folder 793)
    - United States Treasury Department (*), 1873-1885, 1900 (Box 29, Folder 794)
    - United States War Department - James M. Varnum, 1864, 1871-1872, 1879, 1882-1883, 1887, 1895-1897, 1899, 1906, undated (Box 29, Folder 795)
    - Veblen, Thorsten - William F. Vilas, 1880, 1883, 1886, 1888-1889, 1891, 1901, undated (Box 29, Folder 796)
    - Vincent, Boyd - R. D. Volta, 1886, 1888-1892, 1895, 1897-1898, 1908, undated (Box 29, Folder 797)
    - Wade, Edward I. - Treadwell Walden, 1869, 1872, 1882-1883, 1885, 1899, 1904, undated (Box 29, Folder 798)
    - Waldo, Leonard - E. D. Walker, 1870, 1873, 1877, 1881, 1887, 1889, undated (Box 29, Folder 799)
    - Walker, Francis A. (*), 1874-1875, 1877-1878, 1882-1884, 1886, undated (Box 29, Folder 800)
    - Walker, George - Durbin Ward, 1874, 1877, 1879-1881, 1883-1886, 1889-1890, 1893-1895 (Box 29, Folder 801)
    - Ward, Fred B. (*), 1880-1890 (Box 29, Folder 802)
    - Ward, M. - William H. Ward, 1869, 1872, 1880-1882, 1885, 1887, 1890-1891, 1893, undated (Box 29, Folder 803)
    - Warner, Ezra J. - D. F. Warren, 1868, 1871-1872, 1899, (1908) (Box 29, Folder 804)
    - Warren, D. R. - G. Warring, 1878, 1882, 1884, 1890, 1900-1901, 1903, undated (Box 29, Folder 805)
    - Warren, Mortimer A.
      See: box 18, folder 475
    - Washburn, E. A. (*), 1868-1873, undated (Box 29, Folder 806)
    - Washburn, Fanny L. - William E. Waters, 1869, 1871, 1877, 1880 1883, 1887, 1890, undated (Box 29, Folder 807)
    - Watson, W. S. - Henry Watterson, 1875, 1883-1884, 1888, 1890, 1897, 1899, 1901 (Box 29, Folder 808)
    - Wayland, Francis (*), 1875-1895, undated (Box 29, Folder 809)
    - Wayland, Martha W. - Francis H. Weeks, 1869, 1871, 1873, 1876, 1879, 1881, 1884, 1887, 1890, 1896, 1898, undated (Box 29, Folder 810)
    - Weir, T. T. - John B. Welch, 1888, 1890-1891, undated (Box 29, Folder 811)
    - Welch, Lewis S., 1896-1906, undated (Box 29, Folder 812)
    - Welles, G. - Merritt H. Wellman, 1869, 1876, 1885 (Box 29, Folder 813)
    - Wells, David A. (*), 1872-1878, 1885-1895, undated (Box 29, Folder 814-817)
    - Wells, David A. (*), undated (Box 30, Folder 818-819)
    - Wells, D. Collin - Herbert Welsh, 1871, 1881-1882, 1885-1886, 1889, 1898-1901, 1904, undated (Box 30, Folder 820)
    - Welter, H. (*), 1887-1889 (Box 30, Folder 821)
    - Wendell, B. Rush, Jr. - John Wescott, 1880, 1882-1883, 1907, 1909 (Box 30, Folder 822)
    - Wesson, Charles H., 1863-1867 (Box 30, Folder 823-825)
    - Wesson, Charles H. (*), 1868 (Box 30, Folder 825a)
    - Wesson, Charles H. (*), 1869, 1871-1872, undated (Box 30, Folder 826)
    - Wesson, E. B. - A. D. Wetherell, 1868-1869, 1876, 1883-1885, 1888, 1897-1898, 1903-1904 (Box 30, Folder 827)
    - Wetmore, George Peabody - Arthur M. Wheeler, 1872-1873, 1875, 1877, 1881-1883, 1886-1887, 1897-1898, undated (Box 30, Folder 828)
    - Wheeler, Everett P. - Wilson C. Wheeler, 1871, 1875-1876, 1882-1883 1885, 1889 (Box 30, Folder 829)
    - Wheeler, Everett P.
      See: box 17, folder 467
    - Wheelock, William A. (*), 1869-1872, undated (Box 30, Folder 830)
    - Wheelwright, L. A. - Henry C. White, 1877, 1880, 1882, 1884, 1888-1889, 1891, 1895 (Box 30, Folder 831)
    - White, Horace (*), 1877, 1881, 1883-1886, 1888-1890, 1895-1896, 1898 1900 (Box 30, Folder 832)
    - James T. White and Company - William M. Whitelard, 1878-1879, 1882-1883, 1889-1890, 1896-1898, 1900-1901, 1903, 1908, undated (Box 30, Folder 833)
    - Whiteley, William G. - Ernest Whitney, 1866, 1870, 1879-1880, 1882, 1884, 1891, 1893, 1895-1896, 1904, 1908, undated (Box 30, Folder 834)
    - Whitney, Flora Payne (*), undated (Box 30, Folder 835)
    - Whitney, Henry M. (*), 1863-1866, 1869, 1873-1875, 1885, 1901, undated (Box 30, Folder 836-837)
    - Whitney, James L. (*), 1877-1883 (Box 30, Folder 838)
    - Whitney, Margaret D. - Mary S. Whitney, 1895, 1897, 1899, n.d (Box 30, Folder 839)
    - Whitney, William C., 1863-1865 (Box 30, Folder 840-841)
    - Whitney, William C. (*), 1866-1877 (Box 30, Folder 842-844)
    - Whitney, William C., 1878-1885, 1890-1891, 1899, 1901 (Box 30, Folder 845)
    - Whitney, William C. (*), undated (Box 30, Folder 846)
    - Whitney, William Dwight, 1873, 1881, 1884-1885, 1889, 1893, undated (Box 30, Folder 847)
    - Whitridge, Frederick W. - Charles B. Wilby, 1870-1871, 1880, 1884, 1898-1900, 1903, undated (Box 31, Folder 848)
    - Wilcox, Julius (*), 1873-1885 (Box 31, Folder 849)
    - Wilcoxen, J. - George D. Wilder, 1869-1870, 1872, 1874, 1880, 1882-1883, 1890, 1894, 1896, 1903, undated (Box 31, Folder 850)
    - Wiley, Charles S. - Samuel G. Willard, 1867, 1884, 1886, 1888, 1892, 1897-1898 (Box 31, Folder 851)
    - Willard, S. P., 1896, 1900, (1903), 1904 (Box 31, Folder 852)
    - Willcox, C. P. - J. Williams, 1863, 1872, 1882, 1885, 1887, 1895-1896, 1903, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 853)
    - Willcox, W. F.
      See: box 1, folder 14
    - Williams, J. W. - H. Bowlby Willson, 1875-1876, 1878-1879, 1885-1886, 1890, undated (Box 31, Folder 854)
    - Wilshire, H. G. - Verna O. Wilson, 1879-1881, 1884-1885, 1887, 1890-1891, 1901, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 855)
    - Winchester, Charlotte - Fred B. Wood, 1883-1885, 1888, 1890, 1892, 1898, 1900-1901, 1904 (Box 31, Folder 856)
    - Wood, G. W. - A. B. Woodford, 1876-1877, 1879, 1882, 1885-1888, 1892, 1894, 1897, 1907 (Box 31, Folder 857)